[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Wait a moment!
-I'm a lawyer!
-Stay back.
-Which police station are you from?
Mr. Uramawashi!
That reporter,
why did he sue Mr. Uramawashi?
I'm arresting you on suspicion
of threatening Ryutaro Sunaga.
We tricked them.
Maybe they did it out of spite.
If Mr. Uramawashi is gone,
what happens to me as a part-timer?
Study architecture for a while.
Fine, but I'm not doing overtime!
You always go home on time.
That's typical of you.
What's wrong, Sabayama?
"What's wrong?"
This is no time to be asking that!
Mr. Uramawashi has been arrested!
How can you be so calm about it?
Well… you know…
Up until now, I've acted
on Mr. Uramawashi's instructions.
I've walked on fire many times.
But it was always fine.
Because his plans were perfect.
He was always four steps ahead.
But now the man himself has been arrested.
-Maybe we'll get caught too.
-No, that won't…
Besides, why do we have
to keep doing these things?
I am an architect!
A first-class architect!
And this is
an architectural office, right?
Calm down.
-Let's settle down.
-Shut up!
I'm going home.
Sabayama!
I never thought…
I would end up sitting on this side.
I don't think making Mr. Sunaga write
a retraction article about Ms. Shiramoto
constitutes a threat.
Besides, that article wasn't even
in the published magazine.
Mr. Uramawashi,
did you threaten Mr. Sunaga
with something else?
I didn't.
Then… Why were you arrested?
It's a warning.
A warning?
Huh?
Because you're digging into
Ms. Shiramoto's wrongful conviction?
Does it have something to do
with Representative Furuse too?
It's a warrantless arrest.
I'll get you out as soon as possible.
Are you planning on being
my defense lawyer?
What?
Don't do anything unnecessary.
Mr. Uramawashi?
Eto, sorry for calling you
when you're so busy.
It's fine.
I had things I wanted to talk about too.
Oh, but how are things
at Mr. Kureta's office?
Things are so bad.
We barely do any architecture.
What?
You barely do architecture?
At an architectural office?
Oh, no, I mean…
I followed Mr. Kureta
because he talked me into it,
but I'm sick of all the things
he makes me do.
I shouldn't have quit Kyosue Construction.
How about you?
I bet you must be doing well.
You were the star of our class, after all.
Fast-tracking to the top, huh?
Not really.
Did something happen?
I've been asked to design
a new French restaurant,
but things just won't move forward.
They didn't like the design.
They didn't like your design?
Who the heck is the client?
The owner is the chef Kohei Kajiwara.
Do you know Trompe-l'œil?
That famous three-star restaurant.
Of course I know it!
Well, that Chef Kajiwara
just won't give me the go-ahead.
And it seems the project
even has ties to politicians,
so the company is pressuring me,
saying we'll be in trouble if we fail.
I still have other clients too,
so I'm at my limit and at my wits' end.
But…
If this project doesn't come together…
Hey, Sabayama.
Won't you help me with the designs
for Trompe-l'œil?
-Me?
-Yeah.
Your free-spirited designs
might be the breakthrough.
-You're pulling my leg!
-I'm not!
Please.
Let's work together again.
Attorney Miyuki Shiramoto,
arrested on suspicion of murder,
still continues to vehemently
deny the charges.
Yukari.
You know there's no way
I can kill someone, right?
That's right.
Defendant Miyuki Shiramoto
is sentenced to 15 years in prison.
220 days of pre-trial detention
shall be included in the sentence.
Why aren't you appealing?
You were denying the charges
consistently before!
Something happened, right?
Miss,
please talk to me.
Ms. Shiramoto, if you don't hurry,
the appeal deadline will pass.
Miss…
Miss, please tell me what happened.
This isn't right!
I'm sorry,
Yukari.
And then, I barely made it to the trial.
It was a really close call.
I wish someone had woken me up.
You're not asking about it today?
The case, I mean.
If I come here
and just ask about the case every time,
it would just make you sad, Ms. Shiramoto.
Thank you.
You know that lawyer we always talk about?
Yes.
That strange man?
He was suddenly arrested.
What?
That lawyer…
His name is Naoto Uramawashi.
Do you know him?
No.
Is that so?
-Chef Kajiwara is here.
-Oh, let him in.
Chef Kajiwara, I was waiting for you.
Come in.
We'd like you to manage the restaurant,
the food court,
and every section related to food.
You will be the general manager.
Of course, we're counting on you
for future plans as well.
Thank you very much.
I'm showcasing a new menu
today, so I must go.
Okay, please keep up the good work.
How are things with the new restaurant?
I haven't been presented
with a satisfying design yet.
Kyosue Construction, right?
I introduced them because I heard
they were capable.
I see…
I'll contact them on my end.
The new restaurant won't just
get your name out into the world.
It will be a crucial cornerstone
for our plans.
Let's both put more effort into it.
Yes. Please, excuse me.
MOST EXCEPTIONAL RESTAURANT OF THE YEAR
For appetizers,
the cross-section should face 6 o'clock.
Okay.
The main dishes
should be in front to create depth.
Yes.
This plate is missing sauce.
Add a little more.
Understood.
Be careful not to ruin the sugar work.
Yes, understood.
-Bonjour, chef.
-How are the preparations?
Everything will be ready shortly.
I see.
Do you want a taste?
No, it's fine.
Understood.
I leave everything up to you.
Should be no problem, right?
Yes.
The cauliflower soup
has such a pleasant hint of hazelnut!
It's wonderful!
Thank you.
The apple sauce on the meat dish
tasted like fall!
-And the colorful salmon…
-Higuchi.
You're lucky to have
such a wonderful master.
You need to become like Chef Kajiwara.
I agree.
Can you face this way?
Thank you!
This way, please.
WEEKLY TIMES
There you are! I heard the news.
Mr. Uramawashi got arrested
And Sunaga is the one
who sued him for damages?
That's right.
We thought we had him cornered, but…
You'll have to just ask him directly.
Mr. Kureta,
I've decided to help Eto with his work.
Eto from your days at Kyosue Construction?
Yes.
Of course,
I'll still do my job here properly.
Sure.
What do you mean you were threatened?
Wasn't that basically a threat?
Besides, I was told to sue him
for damages.
By whom?
Well…
If you don't tell me,
I'll expose your fabricated articles.
-You're threatening me too?
-Threatening you?
You did write fake articles, right?
Fine.
I was told that if I sued,
I wouldn't have to face threats like that.
But by whom?
A Korean man visited me.
He told me,
"We'll handle the rest, don't worry."
I won't take orders from you anymore.
Why is that?
Don't ask me "why"!
Because I am an architect!
Are you listening?
Yeah, and?
Why does an architect like me
always have to cross
such dangerous bridges…
I mean, design such dangerous bridges?
Remember Eto from Kyosue Construction?
I remember.
I'm going to help create a design
for a new Trompe-l'œil restaurant.
I've been to that place a few times.
If this project comes together nicely…
No, nothing.
Also, may I use your office?
It's an important project,
so I want to concentrate.
Feel free.
Well then.
We may never meet again.
Thanks for everything.
This is a flawless design.
Knowing you, I bet you faithfully
materialized Chef Kajiwara's order.
Yeah.
What did he request?
Well…
Chef Kajiwara only gives
the final judgment.
What?
Then who made the order?
Higuchi. The sous chef.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Where is Chef Kajiwara going?
I've been with Chef Kajiwara
for 20 years now.
He taught me everything
about cooking and this restaurant.
I understand well what he wants.
Please leave the new restaurant to me.
So this design was made with Mr. Higuchi?
Yes, he said
this was what Chef Kajiwara wanted.
Yet, Chef Kajiwara
won't give final approval.
Why?
I don't know! That's why I'm stuck.
If the design isn't put together
by the deadline…
A simple "sorry" won't cut it.
All right,
for now, can I talk to Mr. Higuchi too?
Set up the kitchen like a stage,
and light only the kitchen brightly.
Dim the seating area a bit,
so the kitchen stands out.
He wants customers to see
everything right in front of them,
from cooking to plating.
A restaurant where the chef is the star?
Yes, because our chef
is Mr. Kohei Kajiwara.
I see.
Yet you still can't get approval
from the man himself?
Yes…
I thought he would be pleased
with this design.
How's it going?
Don't just walk in uninvited!
And don't look at my stuff!
I think…
It's more boring than your usual designs.
Huh?
That's Trompe-l'œil, right?
Yeah.
That Chef Kajiwara is eccentric,
or rather, quite a weirdo, isn't he?
I bet it will be tough, but do your best.
Chef Kajiwara?
A weirdo?
KOHEI KAJIWARA
What a lovely office.
Thank you for contacting me.
It's nothing.
I spent every day in loneliness.
What?
Because I went so long without seeing you.
I wanted to see you too.
Because…
I need to ask you something, Donghyuk.
What is it?
Do you know Mr. Sunaga from Weekly Times?
Mr. Sunaga?
Yes, he's an interesting person.
Hoshino apartments'
Mr. Hoshino also told me…
It was you who bought his land
in Konan City, right?
Was that your goal from the start,
when you approached that property?
Well, what is it?
The time I spent with you
was a lot of fun.
Whenever I met you, I always thought this…
You are naively honest.
Donghyuk,
who on earth are you?
Whoever I am,
is none of your business.
I thoroughly researched Chef Kajiwara
and made this.
What is this?
I thought it might be interesting
if a Japanese paper umbrella
stood tall right in the middle
of a French restaurant.
Is it no good?
It's a bit too eccentric, I suppose.
What is this?
The new design, apparently.
Chef Kajiwara,
I was in charge of this design.
My name is Sabayama. I'm an architect.
This design was created
based on a paper umbrella.
One from Gifu Prefecture.
Gifu?
Chef, if I recall,
you are originally from Gifu.
This umbrella is the main pillar.
I imagined it as you,
who is the main pillar of this restaurant.
Escoffier ran his kitchen
like a military brigade.
A brigade without a general will fail.
What he truly cared about was the time
it took for a dish to reach the table.
Brillat-Savarin said that…
The dining table is the only place
where a person is never bored.
What?
Excuse me, Kajiwara
sometimes uses strange expressions.
Escoffier, Brillat-Savarin.
He really is a weirdo.
He's like Mr. Uramawashi.
You mean that Mr. Uramawashi?
Oh, you remember?
Of course.
Come to think of it,
he became a lawyer, right?
-Do you still hang out with him?
-What?
Well, you could say that, yeah.
Did your health take a turn for the worse?
My blood pressure is a bit high.
You have to be careful.
Chef,
I've wanted to ask you for a while.
Why won't you approve Eto's design?
His design is wonderful.
If I'm to be in charge of the new
restaurant, I want that design.
About that…
"We may never meet again."
Didn't you say that?
Could you…
Take a look at this for a moment?
A well-made design.
However, it won't pass.
How do you know?
It is not what Chef Kajiwara ordered.
Am I right?
Yes.
Actually, it was designed after talking
with Mr. Higuchi, the sous chef.
Mr. Higuchi was apparently entrusted
with the design, but in the end,
Chef Kajiwara wouldn't give
the final approval, so they're stuck.
Did you meet Chef Kajiwara?
I met him, but he was a really weird guy.
I couldn't understand what he said.
And that's why you came here today?
-Because I'm a weirdo.
-Yes.
No! I didn't mean it that way.
Gaudí had an assistant named Berenguer.
For 30 years, he turned
Gaudí's concepts into drawings,
managed the construction sites,
and brought the architecture into reality.
But the fame belonged to Gaudí alone.
And?
I wonder what Berenguer
actually felt, back then.
What?
You should be able to draw it too.
The blueprint of lies.
BORROWING
To give shape to a blueprint of lies,
you need a draft.
I can't do it alone.
BORROWING
-I'll start working on the model.
-Yeah, make it at 1:50 scale.
We're low on styrene board, I'll buy some.
Please do.
I have no other choice.
Hello.
Please! Help me out!
What the… you went to visit
with Mr. Uramawashi after all.
I had no choice!
I couldn't understand a thing
Chef Kajiwara was saying.
So you went to ask him
how to draw up the blueprints?
Yes.
But since his face is known to the target,
he wants us to cooperate.
Isn't he asking too much?
Come on, it's fine.
This is basically
Mr. Uramawashi asking us.
I've wanted to ask this for a while,
but why do you all
go so far for Mr. Uramawashi?
It's because we owe him
a debt of gratitude.
Gratitude?
There's no use hiding it. Right, Habu?
Yeah.
Back in the day,
I hit on a girl, but it turned out
she was waiting for her boyfriend.
He came at me,
so I shoved him away,
and he hit his head a bit.
The guy just happened to be Yakuza.
And things got really complicated.
Then, Mr. Uramawashi fabricated
some evidence to get me out of trouble.
The heck?
Come on, Ms. Konno, you too.
-I have to say it too?
-We're on the subject.
Well…
As for me, I got into host clubs
and ended up in debt.
Host clubs?
Yeah, they ran a rip-off operation.
They charged me
some ridiculous interest on my debt,
but Mr. Uramawashi wiped it all out,
including the unpaid tab.
I just kind of admired
Mr. Uramawashi's methods.
That's all.
-Wait, that's all?
-Yeah.
Well, one way or another,
everyone owes that man a favor.
Shall we brainstorm the plan?
-Okay.
-Ça va?
Ça va?
I'm not a French greeting!
Shall I play a college girl this time?
A complete miscast.
I'll come up with ideas.
You're just going to use AI anyway!
It's done.
Our blueprint of lies.
I work as a food coordinator.
My name is Chizuru Saeki.
Actually, I received a request
from a wealthy investor.
They would love to open a restaurant
with you as the chef, Mr. Higuchi.
I see.
Then, regarding the details…
My client himself will explain.
Chef Higuchi, nice to meet you.
My name is Sawahara.
I'll get straight to the point.
I offer you three times
your current salary.
The property, interior, and staff,
I will prepare everything.
You just need to focus purely on cooking.
In fact,
we are already moving forward
with the design.
Something like this.
The kitchen
will be visible from anywhere
inside the restaurant.
The guests can enjoy the chef's cooking
like a performance,
and further savor the dish itself.
A style where you are truly
the star of the show.
If you'd like, shall we go take a look
at the actual property right now?
Huh?
Right now?
-Yes.
I am Kawakami from Saliant Real Estate.
Please, come on in.
May I take a look at the kitchen?
Sure, right this way.
It has everything we need.
This restaurant actually closed down
just the other day.
Of course, you could use it as is,
but we can also renovate it
like the blueprint earlier. Your call.
Well, if I'm going to do it…
You prefer the design we showed you.
Yes, that's right.
Mr. Sawahara,
if you'd like, why don't we talk
at my restaurant?
I'd love to.
Frankly, what do you think
about this proposal?
To be honest,
when I was at that property,
I could picture it.
Myself standing in the spotlight.
So, you will positively consider it, then?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
But, I have one request.
What might that be?
I want to create
a restaurant that surpasses Trompe-l'œil.
However, simply poaching you
won't make that a reality.
Because you are merely
the sous chef under Chef Kajiwara.
What are you trying to say?
I need something that can serve
as the main selling point
of your restaurant, Chef Higuchi.
I had intended
to keep this to myself, but…
For about a year now,
from course composition,
ingredient sourcing and ordering,
menu development,
choosing wine pairings, to even pricing…
I have been entrusted with everything
in the restaurant.
That's hard to believe.
Chef Kajiwara isn't involved at all?
From what I've heard,
Trompe-l'œil is moving forward
with plans for a new location,
but if what you're saying is true,
could that new location
be a restaurant for you?
That was supposed to be the case, but…
About that…
I have no intention
of leaving the new restaurant to you.
How could that be…
Even when I frantically created menus,
composed courses, made customers happy,
the one who took credit was always…
For the past year,
when I make dishes,
he doesn't taste them at all.
In other words,
my cooking no longer
requires his checking.
It means my cooking
has reached a level good enough
to be served under the name
of Kohei Kajiwara.
I've stood shoulder to shoulder
with Kajiwara.
Surpassing him is only a matter of time.
Besides…
-Besides?
-No.
Just between you and me…
It seems his health isn't doing so well.
Huh?
He's always taking medication.
So please rest assured, Mr. Sawahara.
I will definitely surpass this restaurant.
Yes, that is more than enough.
I feel incredibly reassured.
He's quite the gentleman,
that guy Donghyuk.
A gentleman?
By getting me arrested,
he clearly demonstrated where he stands.
Huh?
So he was an enemy, after all.
Could it be…
It would be best
if Sunaga's article got published.
But if it isn't published,
we would know that Furuse
pressured people not to publish it.
If that happened,
someone would make a move.
And that someone was Donghyuk.
By doing so, it became clear
who was on the enemy side,
and we could also see Furuse's movements.
You purposely got arrested
just to get Furuse to act.
Mr. Uramawashi,
you must have a bigger endgame.
Isn't it about time you told me?
Sorry.
The next guest is waiting.
I see,
so there really was a Berenguer
behind Gaudí.
How did you realize that, Mr. Uramawashi?
I went to Trompe-l'œil a few times.
At some point, the taste changed slightly.
A certain quirk.
A quirk?
Berenguer imposed
his own tastes onto the food.
"The one who made this is me."
However,
not all the lies have been uncovered yet.
What?
The real reason Gaudí
entrusted the work to Berenguer.
I'm telling you, it's true!
It's my restaurant!
I'll poach you from Trompe-l'œil too,
so come with me!
Huh?
Why?
He said this place closed down!
What is the matter?
Huh?
I believe today will be the final check.
Are you confident in what you created?
Yes.
I've completed your ideal design,
Chef Kajiwara.
What are you implying?
It's just as you see.
You have no intention
of opening a new restaurant.
No, rather,
you would hate it if a new one was built.
About a year ago, you started
entrusting menu development,
course setup, and everything else
about the restaurant to Mr. Higuchi.
Why did you do that?
Over 20 years,
I have taught Higuchi
everything to know about cooking.
He possesses the skill to handle
Trompe-l'œil. That is all.
Is that also the reason you don't taste
the dishes Mr. Higuchi makes?
Yes.
This is the medicine
you've been taking for the past year.
This is zinc, isn't it?
Could you show me
the design you made last time, again?
Yes.
By having my cooking praised,
I earned stars,
was fawned over by the media,
gained fame,
and I lost sight of what was important.
But this…
This is…
This design…
It called out to me.
"Do I want to cling to fame so badly,
I'm willing to tell lies?"
What happened a year ago?
I lost my sense of taste.
An aftereffect from the virus
during the pandemic two years ago.
I have a taste disorder.
Would you like to taste it?
No, it's fine.
That's why you take zinc,
because it is said to be effective
for taste disorders.
When I lost my sense of taste,
I thought about closing the restaurant.
However, I couldn't do that
because of the sponsors.
So, I entrusted it to Higuchi.
I acknowledge Higuchi's skill.
That part wasn't a lie.
Right around then,
you were asked by your sponsors
to open a new restaurant.
I was introduced to a contractor,
and everything was arranged
without my input.
Even though, in this condition,
I can't open a new restaurant.
You thought of entrusting
the new location to him?
I did think about it.
Higuchi seemed up for it as well.
However,
if I did that,
what would happen to this restaurant?
This restaurant, which Higuchi
currently handles entirely.
It would crumble.
Exactly.
That's why you wouldn't accept any design,
right, Mr. Kajiwara?
Yeah.
But…
I've decided to accept it now.
I will accept…
this design.
I bet you knew about the relationship
between Chef Kajiwara
and Mr. Higuchi from the start.
You used this strategy just to make
Mr. Higuchi open his eyes.
There is more to the story
of Gaudí and Berenguer.
What?
Berenguer unfortunately
passed away at a young age.
At that time, Gaudí said,
"I have lost my right hand."
I hope Gaudí's feelings
will reach Berenguer's heart.
THE RADIANT GASTRONOMY GUIDE
Chef.
This restaurant…
I can no longer manage it.
-So--
-Higuchi.
I'm sorry for everything.
What?
It must have been painful.
Having your cooking praised,
yet not being recognized yourself.
But…
It's all right now.
This is your restaurant.
Chef…
I leave Trompe-l'œil in your hands.
Chef Higuchi.
I'm sorry.
I failed to design the new restaurant.
What are you talking about?
Thanks to you, everyone was saved.
Me, Chef Kajiwara, and Mr. Higuchi too.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
More importantly, Sabayama.
I got the manager's approval!
-What?
-I told you, right?
That we should work together again
at Kyosue Construction.
But I couldn't put the design together.
That doesn't matter anymore!
Come back to us.
Thank you for inviting me. I'm happy.
But, I'm going to try
my best where I am now.
Those guys,
they can't do anything without me.
Really?
Why? You said you wished
you hadn't quit our company, right?
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry!
-The heck?
I am terribly sorry.
I was hoping to have you
handle the culinary side…
I see.
I don't really mind.
Even if you have no sense of taste.
Honestly, what we need is your name.
The name Chef Kohei Kajiwara.
Then all the more reason
why I cannot do it.
Excuse me.
Is it fine to leave it like this?
We were ready to announce him
as the food manager for the Expo.
Tough luck.
Shall we look for a replacement?
Understood.
Also, I've taken care
of the Hakari Architecture Office.
Everyone, thank you so much for your help!
That was a close one.
That medicine was just a lucky guess.
I was so nervous.
Inside that bottle was ramune candy.
In the end, Mr. Uramawashi saved us again.
Yeah.
Now I owe Mr. Uramawashi a favor too,
so let's continue working together!
-Yeah.
-Do your best, Sabayama.
Shouldn't it be "Mr."?
Mr. Sabayama?
It's not like I'm your junior
or something!
Excuse me.
Is the boss, Mr. Kureta, here?
That would be me.
We are here for an inspection
from the district's Building Division.
I am Tachibana.
We ask for your cooperation.
There is something I must tell him.
Officials came for an inspection.
So your business was basically suspended?
You know her, right?
Probe into it a little.
Don't mess with me!
Are you Representative Furuse's henchman?
Shall I help you out, as usual?
Congratulations.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.